http://www.westwoodcollegetexas.com/privacy-policy/

Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
Additional information
How we protect your data
What data breach procedures we have in place
What third parties we receive data from
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
Search for:
EmailFacebookInstagramPinterest Search Engine Land: News & Info About SEO, PPC, SEM, Search Engines & Search MarketingGoogle Web Stories ads now available via Display Network Even as more people shop online, searches for ‘available near me’ up over 100% vs. last year Searching for Opportunity: How COOP Careers is Changing the Digital Marketing Hiring Landscape Google, YouTube add user controls to limit alcohol, gambling ads How to compete with Google in the SERPs, make the jump to agency or in-house, and support ‘the doers’ in your organization Google Search Console API gains fresh data & more New key insights from Google’s John Mueller at SMX Google rolls out App campaign type to re-engage existing users Why your content strategy needs both rank-worthy and link-worthy content in the mix New EU regulations compel more transparency for search rankings YouTube remains dominant source of video in top Google ranking positions Google’s December 2020 core update was big, even bigger than May 2020, say data providers Social Shorts: Twitter adds frequency caps, Reddit’s audience grows, Facebook buys Kustomer Video: Alan Rabinowitz on nofollow links and affiliate links Five ways to become a ‘Search Sherpa’ for your own organization Apple’s data-collection ‘nutrition labels’ for apps will begin appearing next week Where Google is placing its bets in 2021 Google December 2020 Core Update rolling out Google: Page experience signals for ranking apply only to mobile Google expands local business message & map query analytics
Adweek FeedDisney Plans Simultaneous Theatrical, Premium Streaming Releases of Raya and the Last Dragon Kelsey SuttonKFC’s CMO Dishes on How Its Mario Lopez-Led, ‘Authentic’ Lifetime Mini-Movie Came Together Richard CollingsPandora Celebrates Holiday Zoom Gatherings With New Campaign Patrick KulpIndependent Agency The Shipyard Acquires Mering Minda SmileyVictoria’s Secret Names a New CMO to Lead the Brand’s Refresh Diana PearlSycamore Got a Bargain For Ann Taylor and Loft, But Is Now Tasked With a Turnaround Richard CollingsFacebook Teams Up With Cultural Institutions on Instagram AR Effects David CohenOgilvy Appoints Global Chief People Officer and Financial Officer Kyle O’BrienTwitter Touts Progress in Inclusion and Diversity Efforts, Despite Pandemic David CohenTim Hortons Wishes Happy Holidays With Message of Diversity and Inclusion Kyle O’Brien Social Media Examiner | Social Media MarketingFacebook Organic and Paid Reach Strategy for Local Businesses Allie BloydHow to Use Instagram for Customer Service Val RazoHow to Expand Your Facebook Ad Targeting to New Audiences Tara ZirkerYouTube Ad Targeting: What Marketers Need to Know Michael StelznerFacebook Lead Form Ads: How to Optimize for Results Allie BloydSocial Media Marketing Trends for 2021: Predictions From the Pros Lisa D. JenkinsHow to Create Instagram Guides: Step-by-Step Setup Jenn HermanTikTok Content Marketing: How to Grow Your Business With TikTok Michael StelznerHow to Create a Google Data Studio Dashboard Chris MercerFacebook Ads for Local Businesses: A Framework for More Revenue Allie BloydGoogle Analytics 4: What Marketers Need to Know Michael StelznerHow to Use LinkedIn Text Ads: The Budget-Friendly Option AJ WilcoxGetting Started With Google Tag Manager: A Beginner’s Guide Chris MercerHow Much Should You Spend on Facebook Ads? Budgeting Steps Allie BloydLaunching With Facebook Ads: How to Sell More With Facebook Michael StelznerHow to Get More B2B Traffic and Leads With Content Joel NomdarkhamHow to Create Meaningful Engagement on LinkedIn: 3 Tips Luan WiseHow to Amplify Your Instagram Influencer Campaigns With Ads Masha VarnavskiInstagram Content Strategy: Creating Content That Draws Customers to You Michael StelznerHow to Repost Instagram Feed Posts, Stories, IGTV, and Reels Jenn Herman Marketing Land – Internet Marketing News, Strategies & TipsThe importance of governance for digital asset management Sitecore announces headless CMS offering CabinetM launches LibraryM, a martech resource DOOH industry moves to standardize ad inventory Reasons why not to buy a shiny new thing Why Predictability is More Important than Speed in Agile Marketing Using AI to replace cookies with context How one CRM platform is helping drive the revenue cycle How marketers can identify the right ABM vendor Salesforce signs agreement to acquire Slack 1-800 Contacts doubles down on the digital customer experience Record growth in online shopping over the holiday weekend Actionable, expert-led SEO & SEM training… happening next week! Social Shorts: Snapchat’s TikTok rival is here, Facebook teams with BBB for ad reviews The outlook for CRM in a COVID and post-COVID world How consumers can earn money from their data Take a peek into PPC routines during Cyber Five week Hubspot and Howard University partner for Center of Digital Business Repurposing an internal digital ad solution for client use Is your transformation strategy really a strategy?
Blog – Neil PatelBest Online Reputation Management Neil Patel4 PPC Tools to Automate Your Ad Campaigns Neil PatelHow to Use Machine Learning to Improve Your Digital Marketing Neil PatelBest Inventory Management Software Neil Patel7 Strategies for Getting More Customer Testimonials (And What to Do With Them) Neil PatelThe Advanced Guide to Facebook Watch Neil PatelStock Photos are Dead: Create These Blog Images Instead Neil PatelBest Time Tracking Software Neil PatelWhy You Should Create Mobile Ads for Engagement (and Not Just Conversion) Neil PatelThe Best Web Hosting Services (In-Depth Review) Neil Patel
